<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
	<title>Animation Videos</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<image>
    	<url>http://websitetalkingheads.com/images/WTH-logo.png</url>
    	<title>WebsiteTalkingHeads.com</title>
    	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com</link>
  </image>
	<description>Animation is a powerful technique that is able to easily explain things step-by-step, and it keeps the attention of the user!</description>
	
<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Healty Choices</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/563WIYb1DCk/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Healty Choices is an example of our Animation Videos.Research indicates that among internet marketing professionals, millennials are tapping more into social media and video production.   Just evaluate the success of youtubers and various social media influencers. These young entrepreneurs are able to create million money businesses by effectively capitalizing on online video production and through their social media know-how. They used social networking to their advantage and getting a popular medium, web videos, to generate a huge audience that they use as funds for advertisers. In such a way, this was how social media influencers are born.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/563WIYb1DCk/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=563WIYb1DCk" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Ring A Rush Driver</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/9cF8lax1Kh4/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Ring A Rush Driver is an example of our Animation Videos.Static advertisements with images together with block letters are becoming a lot more dated and inconsequential. In this fast-paced country of online web videos, those that are able to utilize the advantages having a website video is a ones who might win. For the revolutionary generation of promoting professionals, this is actually where their strenght lies. Creative content creation—primarily by using video production.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/9cF8lax1Kh4/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9cF8lax1Kh4" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Doc Prep</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/81mI5KraWn0/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Doc Prep is an example of our Animation Videos.How do you be competitive? Social media is a ripe environment in addition to a fast medium to give your message to the wide audience. Which can be where the having to pay public, the youthful professionals with funds to burn thrive and spend their time. If you are able to capture their notice, you can efficiently double your web site's traffic or supercharge your sales using the right strategies.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/81mI5KraWn0/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=81mI5KraWn0" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Jet Solution</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/X4chzs0ZE2Q/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Jet Solution is an example of our Animation Videos.It happens to be effective in facts visualization and substantial data driven internet marketing campaigns while staying true to the short and summarized video making type producing viral videos. Just look from our extensive catalog of companies together with organizations that have cheated our unique whiteboard explainer video fashion. If you are not convinced, why don'tyou talk to some of our trusted representatives and get a quote. Benefit from our services, engage in the new millennium and effortlessly enhance your web traffic around.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/X4chzs0ZE2Q/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X4chzs0ZE2Q" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - ITC Consultancy</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/aMKQK40hWIg/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>ITC Consultancy is an example of our Animation Videos.Research has shown that among promotional professionals, millennials are tapping more into web 2 . and video production.   Just glance at the success of youtubers as well as other social media influencers. These young entrepreneurs are able to create million dollar businesses by effectively taking advantage of online video production along with through their social media know-how. They used web 2 . 0 to their advantage and with a popular medium, web videos, to make a huge audience they can use as investment capital for advertisers. To the extent, this was how web 2 . 0 influencers are born.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/aMKQK40hWIg/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aMKQK40hWIg" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Client Notice</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/h26ag1Qpvrs/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Client Notice is an example of our Animation Videos.How do you be competitive? Social media is mostly a ripe environment and then a fast medium to make your message for a wide audience. Which can be where the having to pay public, the teen professionals with capital to burn survive and spend their particular time. If you can actually capture their notice, you can efficiently double your home page's traffic or increase your sales when using the right strategies.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/h26ag1Qpvrs/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h26ag1Qpvrs" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Reason to Believe</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/wK768Vm98j4/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Reason to Believe is an example of our Animation Videos.Video naturally is the way to go. But, not merely takes a simple random video, what an individual demands is some sort of entertaining and engaging summary animated video. That could be right. If you glance at the web videos that dominate social networking traffic, they have this excellent blend of fascinating, energetic and most significantly short videos.  Nonetheless, you also have to tailor made and additionally partner the information which you want to deliver to the video production style that you can create. That is where we come into play. We at talking heads, specialize in Whiteboard animation. A novel and additionally engaging video production style that combines typography and additionally doodle animation with engaging voice-overs that is perfect for infomercials and knowledge heavy presentations.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/wK768Vm98j4/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wK768Vm98j4" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Bower's Electric</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/fA7DibExzHE/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Bower's Electric is an example of our Animation Videos.Video needless to say is the way to go. But, not merely random video, what an individual demands is a entertaining and engaging summary animated video. That could be right. If you glance at the web videos that dominate web 2 . 0 traffic, they have this specific blend of fascinating, energetic and above all short videos.  Nonetheless, you also have to tailor made along with partner the information you want to deliver to the video production style that one could create. That is where we can be found in. We at talking heads, specify in Whiteboard animation. A novel and engaging video production style that combines typography together with doodle animation by using engaging voice-overs that is made for infomercials and facts heavy presentations.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/fA7DibExzHE/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fA7DibExzHE" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Stadium Animation</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/jrKeb2W--EM/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Stadium Animation is an example of our Animation Videos.How do you be competitive? Social media can be described as ripe environment in addition to a fast medium to provide your message to the wide audience. That is where the spending public, the small professionals with funds to burn flourish and spend their own time. If you'll be able to capture their attention, you can efficiently double your web site's traffic or increase your sales with the right strategies.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/jrKeb2W--EM/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jrKeb2W--EM" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Five Star Solutions</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/EEQplZuYclU/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Five Star Solutions is an example of our Animation Videos.Static commercials with images along with block letters are becoming more and more dated and unimportant. In this fast-paced environment of online web videos, those that can utilize the advantages developing a website video may be the ones who will win. For the popular generation of marketing and advertising professionals, this can be where their stand out point lies. Creative content creation—primarily through the use of video production.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/EEQplZuYclU/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EEQplZuYclU" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Riding the School Bus</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/1AP13YBDeO0/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Riding the School Bus is an example of our Animation Videos.Video surely is the way to go. But, not merely takes a simple random video, what the consumer demands is a entertaining and fascinating summary animated video. That's right. If you think about the web videos that dominate social media marketing traffic, they have the following blend of practicing, energetic and most importantly short videos.  Nevertheless, you also ought to tailor made and partner the information that you like to deliver on the video production style which you can create. That is where we come into play. We at talking heads, concentrate on Whiteboard animation. A novel in addition to engaging video production fashion that combines typography and doodle animation using engaging voice-overs that is good for infomercials and knowledge heavy presentations.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/1AP13YBDeO0/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1AP13YBDeO0" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Ring A Rush Delivery</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/Y0JQNT_eq2c/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Ring A Rush Delivery is an example of our Animation Videos.It's effective in data visualization and in depth data driven promoting campaigns while staying true on the short and made clear video making variety of producing viral videos. Just look for our extensive directory of companies together with organizations that have rooked our unique whiteboard explainer video form. If you are not convinced, you will want to talk to your trusted representatives and acquire a quote. Benefit from our services, engage in the new millennium and effortlessly enhance your web traffic around.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/Y0JQNT_eq2c/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y0JQNT_eq2c" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - WanderfulMedia</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/DR2C1mcpHIk/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>WanderfulMedia is an example of our Animation Videos.Research has shown that among marketing professionals, millennials are tapping more into web 2 . 0 and video production.   Just look at the success of youtubers and other social media influencers. These young entrepreneurs are going to create million $ businesses by effectively taking advantage of online video production together with through their web 2 . 0 know-how. They used social media marketing to their advantage and with a popular medium, web videos, to produce a huge audience that they may use as money for advertisers. In a way, this was how social networking influencers are delivered.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/DR2C1mcpHIk/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DR2C1mcpHIk" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Mantel Mount</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/tNeeDsaSzv0/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Mantel Mount is an example of our Animation Videos.How do you remain competitive? Social media is a ripe environment and a fast medium to give your message to somewhat of a wide audience. Which can be where the spending public, the teen professionals with capital to burn flourish and spend their own time. If you may capture their awareness, you can properly double your web-site's traffic or enhance your sales while using the right strategies.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/tNeeDsaSzv0/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tNeeDsaSzv0" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Bullied in Classroom</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/mL9-SrRAjoA/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Bullied in Classroom is an example of our Animation Videos.Video surely is the way to go. But, not simply random video, what the customer demands is a particular entertaining and engaging summary animated video. That is right. If you glance at the web videos that dominate social media marketing traffic, they have this blend of engaging, energetic and above all short videos.  Although, you also ought to tailor made along with partner the information that you like to deliver with the video production style which you could create. That is where we can be found in. We at talking heads, are experts in Whiteboard animation. A novel in addition to engaging video production fashion that combines typography and doodle animation along with engaging voice-overs that is good for infomercials and data heavy presentations.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/mL9-SrRAjoA/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mL9-SrRAjoA" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Thing A Ma Bob</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/01AECkTT41g/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Thing A Ma Bob is an example of our Animation Videos.Video needless to say is the way to go. But, not merely takes a simple random video, what you demands is some sort of entertaining and engaging summary animated video. That could be right. If you evaluate the web videos that dominate social networking traffic, they have this kind of blend of fascinating, energetic and best of all short videos.  Although, you also will need to tailor made and partner the information that you want to deliver to the video production style which you can create. That is where we come into play. We at talking heads, specialize in Whiteboard animation. A novel in addition to engaging video production style that combines typography along with doodle animation along with engaging voice-overs that is made for infomercials and data heavy presentations.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/01AECkTT41g/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=01AECkTT41g" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Animated Phone</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/_PzG2w8-Stw/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Animated Phone is an example of our Animation Videos.Video needless to say is the way to go. But, not just a random video, what an individual demands is some sort of entertaining and getting summary animated video. That is right. If you think about the web videos that dominate social media marketing traffic, they have this kind of blend of partaking, energetic and above all short videos.  Although, you also will need to tailor made along with partner the information that you like to deliver to your video production style which you can create. That is where we can be found in. We at talking heads, are experts in Whiteboard animation. A novel together with engaging video production type that combines typography and doodle animation by means of engaging voice-overs that is designed for infomercials and knowledge heavy presentations.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/_PzG2w8-Stw/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_PzG2w8-Stw" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Animation Video - Entrepreneurs Network</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/videopresentations/animation.php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/mN9cMEnBG6k/mqdefault.jpg" />]]> is an example of our Animation Videos.</description>
	<media:title></media:title>
	<media:description>Entrepreneurs Network is an example of our Animation Videos.How do you spar for customers? Social media can be a ripe environment and then a fast medium to produce your message to a wide audience. That's where the investing public, the vibrant professionals with capital to burn succeed and spend your time. If you may capture their awareness, you can proficiently double your web site's traffic or boost your sales while using right strategies.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/mN9cMEnBG6k/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mN9cMEnBG6k" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>