<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
	<title>Whiteboard Videos</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<image>
    	<url>http://websitetalkingheads.com/images/WTH-logo.png</url>
    	<title>WebsiteTalkingHeads.com</title>
    	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com</link>
  </image>
	<description>A Whiteboard Video from Talking Heads® helps savvy online marketers or companies to get their message across in a powerful and convincing way.  With Talking Heads® you dont just get whiteboard sketch videos. We get spent years studying the art work of persuasion and communication. Your story ought to be told well by professionals. So we have gathered a team of artists and video professionas and we collaborate with you to create your script and customize the images that will be used in your video.  You will end up with a video that tells your story, boosts leads, and increases sales in your product.</description>
	
<item>
	<title>Xanmar - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/FdOqULUaPtI/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Xanmar is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  At Talking Heads'   we specialise in creating whiteboard videos for all purposes.  You can rely on our efficiency and technical competence plus the talents of our highly skilled, experienced team to create a truly spellbinding whiteboard video for your business. You will find that our services remarkably collaborative straight away, all the way to completion of the video.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Xanmar</media:title>
	<media:description>Xanmar is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/FdOqULUaPtI/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FdOqULUaPtI" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>LVNV Loan Officer - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/bwnlCcZOm1A/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[LVNV Loan Officer is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Our prices will be the most affordable and you will probably have many reasons to see others why Talking Heads' is the most different and distinguished company in the business. Call us right now and let our personnel connect wtih you and give you enough ideas on how to go about developing a stunning kind associated with whiteboard video for ones business.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>LVNV Loan Officer</media:title>
	<media:description>LVNV Loan Officer is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/bwnlCcZOm1A/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bwnlCcZOm1A" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Beyond Power - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/jJ1uO7QX9u4/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Beyond Power is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  You can find that whiteboard video a powerful way to get your call to action out. In addition, another important thing about whiteboard videos is the ability to show your idea in many different ways including graphics, images, text and animations may possibly work with your subject. You can also include your logo design inside your video making it come to life.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Beyond Power</media:title>
	<media:description>Beyond Power is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/jJ1uO7QX9u4/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jJ1uO7QX9u4" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>YF Insurance - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/ZLTlpnSfXIE/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[YF Insurance is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  You can get a highly professional whiteboard video from Talking Heads'  and link it with all you website and media accounts. A increasing amount of people are visiting websites and using web 2 . 0 therefore, the digital environment made available from the internet has developed into a highly valuable platform to attain out millions who will take an active interest in your obtains. Today millions are allocated to advertising and one of the incredible advantages of advertising online is that you can to reach out to huge number of potential customers by using easily affordable budget.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>YF Insurance</media:title>
	<media:description>YF Insurance is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/ZLTlpnSfXIE/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZLTlpnSfXIE" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Uber Therm - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/fA2YJ2Q126A/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Uber Therm is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  At Talking Heads'   we specialise in making whiteboard videos for all purposes.  You can rely on our efficiency and technical competence as well as the talents of our renowned, experienced team to create a truly impressive whiteboard video for any business. You will discover that our services extremely collaborative straight away, all the way to completion of the video.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Uber Therm</media:title>
	<media:description>Uber Therm is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/fA2YJ2Q126A/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fA2YJ2Q126A" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Flax Coffee - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/ZQQole13UVg/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Flax Coffee is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  You can get a highly professional whiteboard video from Talking Heads'  and link it with all you website and media accounts. A increasing number of people are visiting websites and using social media therefore, the digital environment furnished by the internet has developed into a highly valuable platform to achieve out millions who may take an active interest in your products and services. Today millions are invested on advertising and one of the many incredible advantages of advertising online is that you are able to reach out to huge number of potential customers with easily affordable budget.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Flax Coffee</media:title>
	<media:description>Flax Coffee is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/ZQQole13UVg/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZQQole13UVg" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>The Asset Exchange - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/7Xqs3pke4YE/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[The Asset Exchange is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  One can find that whiteboard video a highly powerful method to get your message out. In addition, another advantage of whiteboard videos is the ability to show your idea in many different ways including graphics, images, text and animations may possibly work for ones subject. You can also include your brand inside your video making it come alive.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>The Asset Exchange</media:title>
	<media:description>The Asset Exchange is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/7Xqs3pke4YE/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Xqs3pke4YE" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Grady Financial - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/kJke4ajHyOs/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Grady Financial is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Seize your visitors' awareness while boosting your revenue.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Grady Financial</media:title>
	<media:description>Grady Financial is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/kJke4ajHyOs/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kJke4ajHyOs" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Redesigned Retail - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/WYemYjvKcpY/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Redesigned Retail is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Grab your visitors' curiosity while improving your revenue.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Redesigned Retail</media:title>
	<media:description>Redesigned Retail is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/WYemYjvKcpY/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WYemYjvKcpY" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Aeropure Fans - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/mCwZ2AeUwts/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Aeropure Fans is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  You can get yourself a highly professional whiteboard video from Talking Heads'  and link it with your website and media accounts. A increasing number of individuals are visiting websites and using social media marketing therefore, the digital environment supplied by the internet has developed into highly valuable platform to attain out millions who takes an active interest in your obtains. Today millions are invested in advertising and among the list of incredible advantages of advertising online is that you can to reach out to large numbers of potential customers by means of easily affordable budget.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Aeropure Fans</media:title>
	<media:description>Aeropure Fans is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/mCwZ2AeUwts/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mCwZ2AeUwts" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Children's Miracle Network - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/gCU4N2IkD90/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Children's Miracle Network is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  One can find that whiteboard video an extremely powerful way to get your story out. In addition, another feature of whiteboard videos include the ability to show your concept in many different ways including graphics, images, text and animations that you could possibly work with the subject. You can also include your custom logo design inside your video making it come alive.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Children's Miracle Network</media:title>
	<media:description>Children's Miracle Network is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/gCU4N2IkD90/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gCU4N2IkD90" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title> Parts Edge - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/d6AxjWSLSqk/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[ Parts Edge is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Whiteboard videos appeal to the visual along with auditory senses and are highly successful tools to get your point across. Once they grab a viewer's attention they drive the message home quickly along with creating maximum impact. We use skilled voice-over artists for the spoken presentation for the script.  Our voice-over artists have excellent command with the spoken language to get pronunciation and diction. They can do a remarkably impressive delivery with their captivating voice. ]]>
	</description>
	<media:title> Parts Edge</media:title>
	<media:description> Parts Edge is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/d6AxjWSLSqk/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d6AxjWSLSqk" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Four Seasons Maui - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/OvMC97Wtlw8/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Four Seasons Maui is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  At Talking Heads'   we specialise in making whiteboard videos for any purposes.  You'll be able to bank on our efficiency and technical competence plus the talents of our renowned, professional team to create a truly notable whiteboard video for your business. You will discover that our services very collaborative straight away, all the way to completion of the video.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Four Seasons Maui</media:title>
	<media:description>Four Seasons Maui is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/OvMC97Wtlw8/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OvMC97Wtlw8" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Triple E Equipment - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/gNFrWtPMjUc/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Triple E Equipment is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Seize your website's visitors' awareness while supercharging your income.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Triple E Equipment</media:title>
	<media:description>Triple E Equipment is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/gNFrWtPMjUc/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gNFrWtPMjUc" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Get Limitless - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/sabNW-2vdD8/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Get Limitless is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Whiteboard videos capture the visual and auditory senses as they are highly powerful tools to get your point across. Once they grab a viewer's attention they drive the message home quickly along with creating maximum impact. We use experienced voice-over artists in the spoken presentation of the script.  Our voice-over artists have excellent command with the spoken language to get pronunciation and diction. They will do a very impressive delivery with their captivating voice. ]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Get Limitless</media:title>
	<media:description>Get Limitless is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/sabNW-2vdD8/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sabNW-2vdD8" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>G8TD - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/MtwQtgS0-Y4/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[G8TD is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  There are numerous incredible strengths in whiteboard videos. They present the details about your product through a voice over given by a professional speaker who can be male of female per your choice and the suitability with the concept and product you are waiting to promote. These whiteboard videos are designed on highly advanced technical platforms and thus they easily load as they are viewable in any program both on the hand-held devices and PCs. Though short, a lot of work goes inside production of whiteboard videos so that they come out very well in a very precise, appealing and highly engaging manner trying the audience with a impressive message about your company, product or service.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>G8TD</media:title>
	<media:description>G8TD is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/MtwQtgS0-Y4/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MtwQtgS0-Y4" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Pestco - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/ggIBlAXQbEg/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Pestco is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  You can aquire a highly professional whiteboard video from Talking Heads'  and link it with all you website and media accounts. A increasing amount of people are visiting websites and using web 2 . 0 therefore, the digital environment offered by the internet has become a highly valuable platform to reach out millions who usually requires an active interest in your offerings. Today millions are invested in advertising and one of many incredible advantages of advertising online is that you can to reach out to thousands of potential customers using easily affordable budget.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Pestco</media:title>
	<media:description>Pestco is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/ggIBlAXQbEg/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ggIBlAXQbEg" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>OC Tanner - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/09WObf8GuT4/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[OC Tanner is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Seize your visitors' attention while improving your revenue.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>OC Tanner</media:title>
	<media:description>OC Tanner is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/09WObf8GuT4/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=09WObf8GuT4" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Save Pipey - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/QRDh0jdn35I/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Save Pipey is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  You can find a highly professional whiteboard video from Talking Heads'  and link it with all you website and media accounts. A increasing number of people are visiting websites and using social media therefore, the digital environment supplied by the internet has become a highly valuable platform to reach out millions who will take an active interest in your goods and services. Today millions are invested in advertising and one of several incredible advantages of advertising online is that you are able to reach out to good sized quantities of potential customers with easily affordable budget.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Save Pipey</media:title>
	<media:description>Save Pipey is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/QRDh0jdn35I/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QRDh0jdn35I" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Signature Bank - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/w-bc_4SFOAI/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Signature Bank is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  At Talking Heads'   we specialise in creating whiteboard videos for any purposes.  You can bank on our efficiency and technical competence and also the talents of our highly skilled, experienced team to create a truly impressive whiteboard video for your business. You will discover that our services highly collaborative straight away, all the way to completion of the video.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Signature Bank</media:title>
	<media:description>Signature Bank is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/w-bc_4SFOAI/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w-bc_4SFOAI" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>World Book - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/Y2eWEgqdqR4/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[World Book is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  There are numerous incredible merits in whiteboard videos. They present the information about your product through a voice over provided by a professional speaker who can be male of female according to your choice and the suitability to the concept and product you have been looking to promote. These whiteboard videos are set up on highly advanced technical platforms and for that reason they easily load as they are viewable in any graphical user interface both on the handheld devices and PCs. Despite the fact that short, a lot of work goes contained in the production of whiteboard videos to be able to come out very well in a very precise, appealing and highly engaging manner trying the audience with an extremely impressive message about your enterprise, product or service.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>World Book</media:title>
	<media:description>World Book is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/Y2eWEgqdqR4/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y2eWEgqdqR4" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Water Out Now - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/SGI5NYzlZpU/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Water Out Now is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  You can get a highly professional whiteboard video from Talking Heads'  and link it with your website and media accounts. A increasing amount of people are visiting websites and using social media therefore, the digital environment supplied by the internet has developed into highly valuable platform to reach out millions who can take an active interest in your obtains. Today millions are used on advertising and one of the incredible advantages of advertising online is that you can to reach out to large numbers of potential customers with easily affordable budget.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Water Out Now</media:title>
	<media:description>Water Out Now is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/SGI5NYzlZpU/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SGI5NYzlZpU" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Boldt - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/0w56S2ZW0iA/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Boldt is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  One can find that whiteboard video an incredibly powerful way to get your story out. In addition, another feature of whiteboard videos is the ability to present your concept in a number of ways including graphics, images, text and animations that you work for ones subject. You can also include your name in it making it come to life.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Boldt</media:title>
	<media:description>Boldt is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/0w56S2ZW0iA/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0w56S2ZW0iA" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Roche - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/duk4b4tKhV8/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Roche is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Our prices will be the most affordable and you will probably have many reasons to understand others why Talking Heads' is the most completely unique and distinguished company in the industry. Call us now and let our personnel connect wtih you and supply you with enough ideas on what to go about creating a stunning kind from whiteboard video for the business.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Roche</media:title>
	<media:description>Roche is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/duk4b4tKhV8/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=duk4b4tKhV8" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>City Grow - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/49VH2kO2rrY/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[City Grow is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  You can find a highly professional whiteboard video from Talking Heads'  and link it with your website and media accounts. A increasing number of individuals are visiting websites and using social networking therefore, the digital environment supplied by the internet has changed into a highly valuable platform to attain out millions who usually requires an active interest in your products and services. Today millions are invested on advertising and one of many incredible advantages of advertising online is that you are able to reach out to thousands of potential customers along with easily affordable budget.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>City Grow</media:title>
	<media:description>City Grow is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/49VH2kO2rrY/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=49VH2kO2rrY" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Organic Food Delivery - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/qSS1zsEwUEY/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Organic Food Delivery is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  There are some incredible merits in whiteboard videos. They present the details about your product through a voice over provided by a professional speaker who can be male of female as per your choice and the suitability for the concept and product you are looking to promote. These whiteboard videos are produced on highly advanced technical platforms and for that reason they easily load consequently they are viewable in any program both on the hand-held devices and PCs. Despite the fact that short, a lot of work goes inside production of whiteboard videos to make sure they come out very well in a precise, appealing and highly engaging manner trying the audience with a properly impressive message about your business, product or service.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Organic Food Delivery</media:title>
	<media:description>Organic Food Delivery is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/qSS1zsEwUEY/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qSS1zsEwUEY" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Clean It Online - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/BtOISRf-uhA/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Clean It Online is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  You can receive a highly professional whiteboard video from Talking Heads'  and link it with your website and media accounts. A increasing number of individuals are visiting websites and using social networking therefore, the digital environment furnished by the internet has developed into a highly valuable platform to reach out millions who will take an active interest in your products and services. Today millions are used on advertising and one of the many incredible advantages of advertising online is that you are able to reach out to huge number of potential customers with easily affordable budget.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Clean It Online</media:title>
	<media:description>Clean It Online is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/BtOISRf-uhA/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BtOISRf-uhA" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Green Tree Realty - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/KQxTNsgCf9A/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Green Tree Realty is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  There are some incredible merits in whiteboard videos. They present the information about your product through a voice over given by a professional speaker who can be male of female as per your choice and the suitability for the concept and product you are looking to promote. These whiteboard videos are produced on highly advanced technical platforms and so they easily load and are viewable in any ui both on the accessories devices and PCs. Despite the fact that short, a lot of work goes within the production of whiteboard videos to make sure they come out very well in the precise, appealing and highly engaging manner trying the audience with a impressive message about your company, product or service.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Green Tree Realty</media:title>
	<media:description>Green Tree Realty is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/KQxTNsgCf9A/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KQxTNsgCf9A" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>The Asset Exchange - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/7Xqs3pke4YE/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[The Asset Exchange is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  There are many incredible strengths in whiteboard videos. They present the details about your product through a voice over spoken by a professional speaker who can be male of female per your choice and the suitability with the concept and product you are waiting to promote. These whiteboard videos are made on highly advanced technical platforms and for that reason they easily load consequently they are viewable in any interface both on the hand-held devices and PCs. Despite the fact that short, a lot of work goes inside production of whiteboard videos to make sure they come out very well in the precise, appealing and highly engaging manner trying the audience with an incredibly impressive message about what you are promoting, product or service.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>The Asset Exchange</media:title>
	<media:description>The Asset Exchange is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/7Xqs3pke4YE/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Xqs3pke4YE" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>TreYours - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/CNVIT4MD6Lc/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[TreYours is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  One can find that whiteboard video an incredibly powerful method to get your message out. In addition, another feature of whiteboard videos include the ability to show your concept in a variety of ways including graphics, images, text and animations that you may possibly work with the subject. You can also include your name inside your video making it come to life.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>TreYours</media:title>
	<media:description>TreYours is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/CNVIT4MD6Lc/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CNVIT4MD6Lc" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Gorilla Desk - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/LP1eD7uiGqw/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Gorilla Desk is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  There are some incredible strengths in whiteboard videos. They present the details about your product through a voice over spoken by a professional speaker who can be male of female per your choice and the suitability for the concept and product you want to promote. These whiteboard videos are set up on highly advanced technical platforms and thus they easily load and tend to be viewable in any user interface both on the hand-held devices and PCs. Although short, a lot of work goes inside the production of whiteboard videos to help you come out very well in the precise, appealing and highly engaging manner trying the audience with a impressive message about your business, product or service.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Gorilla Desk</media:title>
	<media:description>Gorilla Desk is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/LP1eD7uiGqw/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LP1eD7uiGqw" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Lyon Financial - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/vuJC0fvb6h0/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Lyon Financial is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  You can aquire a highly professional whiteboard video from Talking Heads'  and link it with your website and media accounts. A increasing amount of people are visiting websites and using web 2 . therefore, the digital environment provided by the internet has changed into a highly valuable platform to arrive out millions who may take an active interest in your products and services. Today millions are invested in advertising and one of the many incredible advantages of advertising online is that you can to reach out to thousands of potential customers by using easily affordable budget.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Lyon Financial</media:title>
	<media:description>Lyon Financial is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/vuJC0fvb6h0/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vuJC0fvb6h0" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>eBooks and Audiobooks - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/DEWxc87QgoM/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[eBooks and Audiobooks is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Seize your visitors' attention while boosting your income.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>eBooks and Audiobooks</media:title>
	<media:description>eBooks and Audiobooks is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/DEWxc87QgoM/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DEWxc87QgoM" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Century Resources - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/xxcG9zvzkX8/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Century Resources is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Seize your visitors' curiosity while improving your revenue.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Century Resources</media:title>
	<media:description>Century Resources is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/xxcG9zvzkX8/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xxcG9zvzkX8" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Argonide - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/o1at9aNVC78/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Argonide is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Our prices will be the most affordable and that you will have many reasons to understand others why Talking Heads' is the most completely unique and distinguished company in the market. Call us nowadays and let our personnel connect wtih you and provide enough ideas about how to go about creating a stunning kind of whiteboard video to your business.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Argonide</media:title>
	<media:description>Argonide is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/o1at9aNVC78/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o1at9aNVC78" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Mantel Mount - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/NiaJuVBheB4/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Mantel Mount is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Our prices include the most affordable and that you will have many reasons to understand others why Talking Heads' is the most completely unique and distinguished company in the business. Call us right now and let our personnel interact wtih you and provide enough ideas on how to go about preparing a stunning kind from whiteboard video to your business.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Mantel Mount</media:title>
	<media:description>Mantel Mount is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/NiaJuVBheB4/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NiaJuVBheB4" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>HTA - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/QJzS_f8gVDo/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[HTA is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Our prices could be the most affordable and you'll have many reasons to inform others why Talking Heads' is the most specific and distinguished company in the business. Call us now and let our personnel connect wtih you and present you with enough ideas on how to go about having a stunning kind involving whiteboard video for the business.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>HTA</media:title>
	<media:description>HTA is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/QJzS_f8gVDo/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QJzS_f8gVDo" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Synthetic Grass Warehouse - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/FlfXe1ZHSL0/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Synthetic Grass Warehouse is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  Whiteboard videos fascinate the visual and auditory senses consequently they are highly powerful tools to get your point across. Once they grab a viewer's attention they drive the message home quickly while creating maximum impact. We use professional voice-over artists for the spoken presentation in the script.  Our voice-over artists have excellent command over the spoken language to get pronunciation and diction. They're able to do a really impressive delivery making use of their captivating voice. ]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Synthetic Grass Warehouse</media:title>
	<media:description>Synthetic Grass Warehouse is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/FlfXe1ZHSL0/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FlfXe1ZHSL0" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Palmpons - Whiteboard Video</title>
	<link>http://www.websitetalkingheads.com/whiteboard/index.php</link>
	<description xml:space="preserve">
		<![CDATA[<img src="http://img.youtube.com/vi/LkkHGYxt5hI/mqdefault.jpg" />]]>
		<![CDATA[Palmpons is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.  There are many incredible benefits in whiteboard videos. They present the specifics of your product through a voice over given by a professional speaker who can be male of female according to your choice and the suitability to the concept and product you have been looking to promote. These whiteboard videos are produced on highly advanced technical platforms and so they easily load and they are viewable in any interface both on the portable devices and PCs. Nevertheless short, a lot of work goes contained in the production of whiteboard videos to be able to come out very well in the precise, appealing and highly engaging manner trying the audience with an incredibly impressive message about your enterprise, product or service.]]>
	</description>
	<media:title>Palmpons</media:title>
	<media:description>Palmpons is an example of our Whiteboard Videos.</media:description>
	<media:thumbnail url="http://img.youtube.com/vi/LkkHGYxt5hI/mqdefault.jpg" height="320" width="180"/>
	<media:content url="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LkkHGYxt5hI" medium="video" height="1920" width="1080">
	</media:content>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>